<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved. -->
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='messages.xsl'?>
<staticData language="EN">
	<!--tells the LocStudio XML parser that tags ref and str are to be considered localizable text-->
	<_locDefinition>
		<_locTag _loc="locFull">ref</_locTag>
		<_locTag _loc="locFull">str</_locTag>
	</_locDefinition>
	<!--Error listings start here.-->
	<ecset xmlns:ec="urn:microsoft.com:DFS Replicationerrors">
		<error id="1004" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrsvcrestarting">
			<code _locID="code-1004">The DFS Replication service is restarting frequently. </code>
			<description _locID="description-1004">
				The DFS Replication service has restarted <ref id="1004.1"/> times in the past 7 days. This problem can affect the replication of all replicated folders to and from this server.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1004">
				If you restarted the service manually, you can safely ignore this message. For information about troubleshooting frequent service restart issues, see <str value="1004"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1010" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_SERVICE_INTERNAL_ERROR">
			<code _locID="code-1010">The DFS Replication service has stopped because of an internal error.</code>
			<description _locID="description-1010">
				The DFS Replication service has stopped because of an internal error from which it cannot recover. No content is replicating to or from this server. Error <ref id="1010.3"/> in line <ref id="1010.2"/>. The service will be restarted automatically by the service control manager.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1010">
				If the service fails to restart or if you are seeing this often, you will need to investigate the issue. For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="1010"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1106" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_SERVICE_RESUME_FAILED_AFTER_BACKUP_RESTORE">
			<code _locID="code-1106">The DFS Replication service failed to restart after a backup or restore operation.</code>
			<description _locID="description-1106">
				The DFS Replication service failed to restart after a backup or restore operation. This failure can occur because the service encountered an internal error. The DFS Replication service must be restarted manually.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1106">
				Restart the DFS Replication service either by using the Services snap-in or by typing <b>net start dfsr</b> at the command prompt. For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="1106"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1108" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_SERVICE_FAILED_PROCESSING_RESTORE_VOLUME_LIST">
			<code _locID="code-1108">The DFS Replication service failed to process the list of restored volumes.</code>
			<description _locID="description-1108">
				The DFS Replication service failed to process the list of restored volumes. This failure can occur if the service encountered errors while accessing the list.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1108">
				The service will retry processing the list in <ref id="1108.1"/> minutes.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1112" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_SERVICE_INVALID_AUTH_RESTORE_REQUEST">
			<code _locID="code-1112">Read-only replicated folders cannot be restored authoritatively.</code>
			<description _locID="description-1112">
				The DFS Replication service failed a restore request. This could happen if an attempt was made to restore the contents of a read-only replicated folder authoritatively. Read-only replicated folders should only be restored non-authoritatively. Authoritative restores should be performed only on read-write replicated folders.
				Additional Information:
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="1112.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="1112.2"/>.
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="1202" type="error" sortkey="domaincontrollerunreachable">
			<code _locID="code-1202">
				Domain controller <ref id="1202.1"/> is unreachable.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-1202">
				The DFS Replication service could not contact domain controller <ref id="1202.1"/> to access configuration objects. Replication is currently stopped. The service will attempt to replicate again during the next poll cycle, in <ref id="1202.2"/> minutes. Possible causes of this event include: TCP/IP connectivity, firewall, Active Directory Domain Services, or DNS issues.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1202">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="1202"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1208" type="error" sortkey="unabletostartrpclistener">
			<code _locID="code-1208">Unable to start a RPC listener. </code>
			<description _locID="description-1208">
				The DFS Replication service was unable to start an RPC listener. Replication is currently stopped on this server. This error can be caused by RPC issues, port filtering or a firewall blocking the dynamic end-point mapper. DFS Replication encountered an issue on port <ref id="1208.1"/> with error ID: <ref id="1208.2"/> (<ref id="1208.3"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1208">
				For information about troubleshooting RPC issues see <str value="rpckb"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1302" type="error" sortkey="unabletowritedebuglogs">
			<code _locID="code-1302">Unable to write debug logs. </code>
			<description _locID="description-1302">
				The DFS Replication service cannot write to the debug logs in <ref id="1302.3"/>. The volume might be out of disk space, or the DFS Replication service might not have sufficient security permissions to modify the debug log files.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1302">
				See additional information about disk space under the informational section in the "Amount of disk space used by replicated folders" table. For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="1302"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="1312" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_SERVICE_LOG_INITIALIZATION_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-1312">The DFS Replication service debug logging is disabled.</code>
			<description _locID="description-1312">
				The DFS Replication service encountered errors while configuring the debug log files. Logging is disabled until this error is resolved. Debug log path is <ref id="1312.3"/> and error ID: <ref id="1312.1"/> (<ref id="1312.2"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-1312">
				For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="1312"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2004" type="error" sortkey="diskfull">
			<code _locID="code-2004">
				Volume <ref id="2004.2"/> is full or failing.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2004">
				The DFS Replication service stopped replication on volume <ref id="2004.2"/>. This failure can occur because the disk is full, the disk is failing, or a quota limit has been reached.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2004">
				Increase the available disk space on the specified volume or move the replicated folder to a different volume. See additional information about disk space under the informational section in the "Amount of disk space used by replicated folders" table.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2104" type="error" sortkey="databaseinerrorstate">
			<code _locID="code-2104">
				A database problem is blocking replication on volume <ref id="2104.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2104">
				The DFS Replication service was unable to recover from an internal database error on volume <ref id="2104.2"/>. Replication has stopped for all replicated folders on this volume until the database is automatically rebuilt. If the database is rebuilt successfully, replication will resume after the rebuilding is complete. If the database cannot be rebuilt, a separate event is generated. If you are seeing this error more than two times in seven days, we recommend that you run Chkdsk on the volume that contains the database.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2104">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="2104"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2202" type="warning" sortkey="usnjournalwrap">
			<code _locID="code-2202">
				DFS Replication has experienced an update sequence number (USN) journal wrap on <ref id="2202.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2202">
				A USN journal wrap occurred <ref id="2202.3"/> times in the past 7 days on <ref id="2202.2"/>. DFS Replication monitors the USN journal to detect changes made to the replicated folder. A USN journal wrap occurs when large numbers of files change so quickly that the USN journal must discard the oldest changes (before DFS Replication has had a chance to detect the changes) to stay within the specified size limit of the USN journal. Although DFS Replication automatically recovers from this problem, replication stops temporarily for replicated folders stored on this volume. Repeated journal wraps usually indicate that the USN journal is too small.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2202">
				Increase the size of the USN journal. For more information, see the <str value="2202"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2204" type="warning" sortkey="usnjournalloss">
			<code _locID="code-2204">
				DFS Replication has experienced an update sequence number (USN) journal loss on <ref id="2204.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2204">
				A USN journal loss occurred <ref id="2204.3"/> times in the past 7 days on <ref id="2204.2"/>. DFS Replication monitors the USN journal to detect changes made to the replicated folder. Although DFS Replication automatically recovers from this problem, replication stops temporarily for replicated folders stored on this volume. Repeated journal loss usually indicates disk issues.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2204">
				For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="2204"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2208" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_VOLUME_JOURNAL_RECOVERY_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-2208">
				DFS Replication failed to recover from USN journal wrap or USN journal loss on volume <ref id="2208.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2208">
				DFS Replication will attempt to recover from this problem automatically on volume <ref id="2208.2"/>, but replication will not take place until USN journal recovery is complete. This failure has occurred <ref id="2208.6"/> times in the past 7 days on this volume. <ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2208">
				For more information, see <str value="2208"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="2210" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_VOLUME_JOURNAL_ADD_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-2210">
				The DFS Replication service failed to create an USN journal on volume <ref id="2210.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-2210">
				The DFS Replication service failed to create an NTFS change journal on volume <ref id="2210.2"/>.
				Replication is disabled for all replicated folders on this volume. The volume must
				have at least <ref id="2210.3"/> MB free. Error ID: <ref id="2210.4"/> (<ref id="2210.5"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-2210">
				Ensure you have sufficient disk space. For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="2210"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4004" type="error" sortkey="xontentset">
			<code _locID="code-4004">
				DFS Replication service stopped replication on replicated folder <ref id="4004.6"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4004">
				The DFS Replication service stopped replication on replicated folder <ref id="4004.6"/> at local path <ref id="4004.3"/> due to Error ID: <ref id="4004.4"/> (<ref id="4004.5"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4004">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="4004"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4114" type="warning" sortkey="EVENT_DFSR_CS_DISABLED">
			<code _locID="code-4114">
				One or more replicated folders are not replicating to this member because their memberships are disabled.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4114">
				The replicated folders listed above are not participating in replication because their memberships were manually disabled on this member. 
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4114">
				If you want these replicated folders to participate in replication, enable the desired memberships using the DFS Management snap-in or the Dfsradmin.exe command-line tool.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4202" type="warning" refers2="staging" reports="none" sortkey="prematurepagingofstagingfiles">
			<code _locID="code-4202">Premature purging of staging files is impacting performance on replicated folder <ref id="4202.8"/>. </code>
			<description _locID="description-4202">
				Staging files are being purged prematurely because the staging quota for replicated folder <ref id="4202.8"/> is too small. This purging can cause excessive disk I/O and CPU usage. To avoid this problem, increase the quota of the staging folder. This has occurred <ref id="4202.12"/> times in the past 72 hours.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4202">
				Increase the size of the staging folder. To see best practices for staging folder sizing, see <str value="4202"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4206" type="warning" sortkey="CS_STAGE_CLEANUP_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-4206">
				DFS Replication failed to clean up old staging files for replicated folder <ref id="4206.8"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4206">
				DFS Replication failed to clean up old staging files. As a result, some large files might fail to replicate, and the replicated folder <ref id="4206.8"/> might become out of sync. The service will automatically try to clean up the staging folder again. This failure has happened <ref id="4206.13"/> times in the past 7 days.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4206">
				For more information, see <str value="4206"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4208" type="error" sortkey="stagingexceededsize">
			<code _locID="code-4208">
				Staging folder for replicated folder <ref id="4208.8"/> has exceeded its configured size.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4208">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the staging space usage has exceeded its quota size (<ref id="4208.4"/> MB) for the replicated folder at local path <ref id="4208.2"/>. The service is currently using <ref id="4208.5"/> MB of staging space. The service might fail to replicate some large files and the replicated folder might become out-of-sync. The service is trying to clean up staging space automatically. This has occurred <ref id="4208.12"/> times in the past 72 hours.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4208">
				To resolve this problem, increase the configured size of the staging folder. To see best practices for staging folder sizing, see <str value="4208"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4212" type="error" sortkey="stagingfolaccess">
			<code _locID="code-4212">
				Staging folder <ref id="4212.3"/> cannot be accessed.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4212">
				DFS Replication cannot replicate files in the replicated folders listed above because the staging folder at <ref id="4212.3"/> cannot be opened. Replication can not take place because the service is unable to create staging files.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4212">
				Verify that the staging folder path exists and that the service has access to it.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4302" type="error" refers2="sharing" reports="none" sortkey="sharingviolations">
			<code _locID="code-4302">One or more replicated folders have sharing violations. </code>
			<description _locID="description-4302">
				Due to ongoing sharing violations, DFS Replication cannot replicate files in the replicated folders listed above. This problem is affecting <str value="filecount"/> files in <str value="setcount"/> replicated folders.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4302">
				Verify that the files you want to replicate are closed and have no open handles to them. For information about troubleshooting sharing violations, see <str value="4302"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4304" type="error" refers2="sharing" reports="none" sortkey="sharingviolations">
			<code _locID="code-4304">One or more replicated folders have sharing violations. </code>
			<description _locID="description-4304">
				Due to ongoing sharing violations, DFS Replication cannot replicate files in the replicated folders listed above. This problem is affecting <str value="filecount"/> files in <str value="setcount"/>replicated folders.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4304">
				Verify that the files you want to replicate are closed and have no open handles to them. For information about troubleshooting sharing violations, see the <str value="4304"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4312" type="warning" sortkey="sharingviolationswalking">
			<code _locID="code-4312">
				Sharing violations are preventing replication of a folder in replicated folder <ref id="4312.5"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4312">The DFS Replication service has been repeatedly prevented from getting folder information due to consistent sharing violations encountered on a folder. The service is unable to replicate the folder and files in that folder until the sharing violation is resolved. </description>
			<action _locID="action-4312">
				Verify that the files you want to replicate are closed and have no open handles to them. For information about troubleshooting sharing violations, see the <str value="4312"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4314" type="error" sortkey="SHARING_VIOLATION_CLEANUP">
			<code _locID="code-4314">
				Initial replication for replicated folder <ref id="4314.5"/> is blocked due to sharing violations.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4314">The DFS Replication service has been repeatedly prevented from moving file <ref id="4314.2"/> to the Pre-existing folder due to consistent sharing violations encountered on the file. Initial sync will not be completed until this problem is resolved and local changes will not replicate out.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4314">
				Verify that the files you want to replicate are closed and have no open handles to them. For information about troubleshooting sharing violations, see the <str value="4312"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="4402" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CS_UNSUPPORTED_ENCRYPTED_FILES">
			<code _locID="code-4402">
				Replication of files encrypted by EFS is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-4402">
				The DFS Replication service encountered a file encrypted using the Encrypting
				File System (EFS) in replicated folder <ref id="4402.4"/> with local path <ref id="4402.3"/>. The file <ref id="4402.2"/> will not be replicated
				because the replication of files encrypted by EFS is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4402">
        Replication of files encrypted by EFS is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
      </action>
		</error>
		<error id="4406" type="error" sortkey="EVENT_DFSR_CS_UNSUPPORTED_REPARSE_TAG">
			<code _locID="code-4406">
        Replication of this type of reparse point is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
      </code>
			<description _locID="description-4406">
        The DFS Replication service encountered an unsupported reparse point in replicated
        folder <ref id="4406.4"/> with local path <ref id="4406.3"/>. This reparse point (<ref id="4406.2"/>) will not be replicated because the replication of this
      type of reparse point is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
      </description>
			<action _locID="action-4406">
        Replication of this type of reparse point is not supported by the DFS Replication service.
      </action>
		</error>
		<error id="4502" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_CS_DISK_FULL">
			<code _locID="code-4502">
				DFS Replication unable to replicate files for replicated folder <ref id="4502.3"/> due to insufficent disk space.
      </code>
			<description _locID="description-4502">
				The DFS Replication service was unable to replicate one or more files because adequate free space to replicate the files was not available for staging folder <ref id="4502.9"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-4502">
				Determine whether the volume reported hosts the replicated folder, the staging folder or both as in default configuration. See additional information about disk space under the informational section in the table titled "Current used and free disk space on volumes where replicated folders are stored". Ensure that enough free space is available on the volume for replication to proceed or move the associated replicated folder or staging folder to a different volume that has more free space.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="5002" type="error" refers2="staging" sortkey="rpcerrors">
			<code _locID="code-5002">
				Communication errors are preventing replication with <ref id="5002.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-5002">
				DFS Replication cannot replicate with partner <ref id="5002.2"/> due to a communication error.
				The DFS Replication service used partner DNS name <ref id="5002.4"/>, IP address <ref id="5002.6"/>, and
				WINS address <ref id="5002.5"/> but failed with error ID: <ref id="5002.7"/> (<ref id="5002.8"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-5002">
				Check for network connectivity problems, for troubleshooting RPC issues see <str value="rpckb"/> and for additional troubleshooting information, see <str value="5002"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="5008" type="error" sortkey="rpcerrors">
			<code _locID="code-5008">
				Communication errors are preventing replication with partner <ref id="5008.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-5008">
				DFS Replication cannot replicate with partner <ref id="5008.2"/> due to a communication error.
				This error can occur if the host is unreachable, or if the DFS Replication service is not running on the server.
				The DFS Replication service used partner DNS name <ref id="5008.4"/>, IP address <ref id="5008.6"/>, and
				WINS address <ref id="5008.5"/> but failed with error ID: <ref id="5008.7"/> (<ref id="5008.8"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-5008">
				Check for network connectivity and service related problems. For troubleshooting RPC issues see <str value="rpckb"/> and for additional troubleshooting information, see <str value="5008"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="5012" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CONNECTION_UNRECOGNIZED">
			<code _locID="code-5012">
				Communication errors are preventing replication with partner <ref id="5012.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-5012">
				DFS Replication cannot replicate with partner <ref id="5012.2"/> for replication group <ref id="5012.3"/>. The partner did not recognize the connection or the
					replication group configuration. The DFS Replication service used partner DNS name <ref id="5012.4"/>, IP address <ref id="5012.6"/>, and
					WINS address <ref id="5012.5"/> but failed with error ID: <ref id="5012.7"/> (<ref id="5012.8"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-5012">
				This error can occur when the partner does not have the latest DFS Replication configuration information. The service will retry the connection periodically. For troubleshooting information, , see <str value="5012"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="5102" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_INCOMPATIBLE_VERSION">
			<code _locID="code-5102">
				Communication with partner <ref id="5102.2"/> failed due to incompatible versions of the service.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-5102">
				The DFS Replication service failed to communicate with partner <ref id="5102.2"/>. The version of the communication protocol is different
				on the partner. This server has <ref id="5102.4"/>.<ref id="5102.5"/>, while partner <ref id="5102.2"/> has <ref id="5102.6"/>.<ref id="5102.7"/>. No data is being replicated to or from this partner.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-5102">
				Ensure that the same version of the DFS Replication service is installed on both machines, including any service packs, downloads and hotfixes.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6002" type="error" sortkey="inconsistentconfiguration">
			<code _locID="code-6002">Inconsistent configuration detected (invalid object). </code>
			<description _locID="description-6002">
				The DFS Replication service detected invalid <ref id="6002.1"/> object data while polling for configuration information.
				Additional information includes Object DN: <ref id="6002.2"/> Attribute Name: <ref id="6002.3"/> and domain controller: <ref id="6002.4"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6002">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6002"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6004" type="warning" sortkey="conflictingconfiguration">
			<code _locID="code-6004">Inconsistent configuration detected (conflict). </code>
			<description _locID="description-6004">
				The DFS Replication service detected a conflict between two or more <ref id="6004.1"/> objects while polling Active Directory Domain Services for configuration information. The conflict detected on <ref id="6004.2"/> was resolved by using <ref id="6004.3"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6004">
				You can use the command-line tool Dfsradmin.exe to resolve this issue. For information about troubleshooting this error, see <str value="6004"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6006" type="warning" sortkey="CONFIG_DS_INCONSISTENT_DATA">
			<code _locID="code-6006">Inconsistent configuration detected (missing object). </code>
			<description _locID="description-6006">
				The DFS Replication service detected an inconsistent <ref id="6006.1"/> object while polling domain controller <ref id="6006.4"/> for
				configuration information. The object at <ref id="6006.2"/> references another object
				at <ref id="6006.3"/> that does not exist.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6006">
				The service will try polling again in <ref id="6006.5"/> minutes. If the problem continues, <str value="6006"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6008" type="error" sortkey="invalidparameter">
			<code _locID="code-6008">Bad configuration parameter. </code>
			<description _locID="description-6008">
				The DFS Replication service detected a bad parameter in <ref id="6008.1"/>
				<ref id="6008.2"/> configuration. The parameter of <ref id="6008.3"/> is <ref id="6008.4"/>. The service cannot recover from this error and will disable the <ref id="6008.5"/> in question until the parameter is fixed.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6008">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6008"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6010" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_CONFIG_INVALID_PARAMETER_WARNING">
			<code _locID="code-6010">Bad configuration parameter.</code>
			<description _locID="description-6010">
				The DFS Replication service detected a bad parameter in <ref id="6010.1"/>
				<ref id="6010.2"/> configuration.
				The parameter <ref id="6010.3"/> is <ref id="6010.4"/>. The service has ignored the input value and used the default [<ref id="6010.5"/>] instead.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6010">
				For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6010"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6012" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_CONFIG_DS_INVALID_SCHEMA_VERSION">
			<code _locID="code-6012">The DFS Replication service detected that required Active Directory Domain Services schema objects are not available. </code>
			<description _locID="description-6012">
				The DFS Replication service detected that required Active Directory Domain Services schema objects are not available on domain controller <ref id="6012.4"/>. DFS Replication expected <ref id="6012.2"/> but found <ref id="6012.3"/>. This problem can occur if the schema was not upgraded, the schema partition has not yet replicated to domain controller <ref id="6012.4"/>, or if the version of the schema is incompatible. The service will try again in the next Active Directory Domain Services poll cycle <ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6012">
				Please make sure the required schema upgrade has been applied to the Forest and that Active Directory Domain Services replication of the Schema partition was able to reach this Domain Controller. For more information, see  <str value="6012"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6016" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_CONFIG_DS_UPDATE_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-6016">The DFS Replication service failed to update configuration in Active Directory Domain Services.</code>
			<description _locID="description-6016">
				The DFS Replication service failed to update configuration in Active Directory Domain Services.
				This operation will be retried in the next polling cycle. The service attempted to connect to domain controller <ref id="6016.5"/> and failed with error ID: <ref id="6016.3"/> (<ref id="6016.4"/>).
				Additional information includes object category: <ref id="6016.1"/> and object DN: <ref id="6016.2"/>.
				Replication may be disabled until this error is fixed.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6016">
				The service will retry this operation periodically. For more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6016"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6020" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_DS_RG_NO_OUTBOUND_CONNECTIONS">
			<code _locID="code-6020">A read-write replicated folder is configured with only one way connections.</code>
			<description _locID="description-6020">
				The replication group <ref id="6020.2"/> contains a read-write replicated folder. The DFS Replication service has detected that there is no outbound connection between this server and any of its replication partners. Setting up a read-write replicated folder with only a one-way connection to a replication partner is not a supported configuration. Please create the missing outbound connection to this server using the DFS Management console in order to fix this broken replication topology.
				Additional Information:
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="6020.1"/> ; 
				Member ID: <ref id="6020.3"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6020">
				 Please create the missing outbound connection to this server using the DFS Management console in order to fix this broken replication topology.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6022" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_DS_RG_NO_INBOUND_CONNECTIONS">
			<code _locID="code-6022">A read-only replicated folder is configured with no inbound connections.</code>
			<description _locID="description-6022">
				The replication group <ref id="6022.2"/> contains a read-only replicated folder. The DFS Replication service has detected that there is no inbound connection to this server from any of its replication partners. An inbound connection from a member hosting a read-write copy of this replicated folder is required so that the DFS Replication service can keep the contents of the read-only replicated folder up to date. Please create the missing inbound connection to this server using the DFS Management console in order to fix this broken replication topology.
				Additional Information:
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="6022.1"/> ; 
				Member ID: <ref id="6022.3"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6022">
				Please create the missing inbound connection to this server using the DFS Management console in order to fix this broken replication topology.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6104" type="error" sortkey="wmiregistrationfailed">
			<code _locID="code-6104">Registration failed for the DFS Replication service providers. </code>
			<description _locID="description-6104">
				The DFS Replication service failed to register the Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) providers with error ID: <ref id="6104.1"/> (<ref id="6104.2"/>). The DFS Replication service requires a WMI provider on each member of the replication group.
				This provider is used to collect diagnostics and operational information. If the provider cannot be registered, this information cannot be collected and replication is disabled for all replicated folders on this server.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6104">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6104"/> and <str value="wmi"/> to resolve the error string.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6302" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CONFIG_VOLUME_NOT_SUPPORTED">
			<code _locID="code-6302">
				Volume <ref id="6302.2"/> is not supported for DFS Replication.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6302">
				The DFS Replication service is unable to start replication on volume <ref id="6302.2"/> because
				the volume is not supported.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6302">
				Ensure that the volume is a local, non-removable volume formatted using the NTFS file system.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6402" type="error" sortkey="overlappingfrscontentsets">
			<code _locID="code-6402">Replicated folder <ref id="6402.5"/> overlaps with an FRS replica set. </code>
			<description _locID="description-6402">
				The DFS Replication service cannot replicate the replicated folder <ref id="6402.5"/> at local path <ref id="6402.4"/> because it overlaps with a folder <ref id="6402.3"/> that is replicated using File Replication service (FRS). This configuration is unsupported.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6402">
				Fix this problem by not overlapping this replicated folder with an FRS replica set. That is, do not replicate the same local path using DFS Replication and FRS.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6404" type="error" sortkey="invalidfolderpath">
			<code _locID="code-6404">
				The replicated folder <ref id="6404.3"/> has an invalid local path.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6404">
				DFS Replication cannot replicate the replicated folder <ref id="6404.3"/> because the local path <ref id="6404.2"/> is not the fully qualified path name of an existing,
				accessible local folder. This replicated folder is not replicating to or from this server.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6404">
				Fix this problem by pointing the replicated folder to a valid local path using the DFS Management snap-in or the Dfsradmin.exe command-line tool.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6406" type="warning" sortkey="DFSR_CONFIG_CS_ROOT_STALE">
			<code _locID="code-6406">
				Local path of replicated folder <ref id="6406.4"/> does not match the newly configured local path.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6406">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the local path of a replicated folder
				<ref id="6406.2"/> in its database does not match the newly configured local path <ref id="6406.3"/> of the
				replicated folder <ref id="6406.4"/>. The service will replicate the new path, and the old replicated
				folder path in the database will no longer be tracked as a replicated folder.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6406">
				This event is expected if the local path of the replicated folder has been changed. If this is not the case, for more information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6406"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6408" type="error" sortkey="overlappingdfsrcontentsets">
			<code _locID="code-6408">Overlapping replicated folders (<ref id="6408.5"/> and <ref id="6408.11"/>) were detected. </code>
			<description _locID="description-6408">
				The DFS Replication service cannot replicate the replicated folder <ref id="6408.5"/> at local path <ref id="6408.4"/> because it overlaps with the replicated folder <ref id="6408.11"/> at local path <ref id="6408.10"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6408">
				Fix this problem by not overlapping these replicated folders i.e. point each folder to a unique local path.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6410" type="error" sortkey="overlappingwithsystemfolder">
			<code _locID="code-6410">
				Replicated folder <ref id="6410."/> is overlapping with Windows system folder.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6410">
				The DFS Replication service failed to initialize replicated folder <ref id="6410.2"/> because it detected that one of its working folders (<ref id="6410.3"/>) overlaps with a Windows system folder. Replication is not taking place because this is an unsupported configuration.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6410">
				Reconfigure the replicated folder so that none of its working folders overlaps a Windows system folder.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6412" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CS_OVERLAPPING_WITH_LOG">
			<code _locID="code-6412">
				Replicated folder <ref id="6412.2"/> is overlapping with debug log folder.
            </code>
			<description _locID="description-6412">
				The DFS Replication service failed to initialize replicated folder <ref id="6412.2"/> because
				the service detected that one of its working folders <ref id="6412.3"/> overlaps with the debug log
				folder <ref id="6412.9"/>. Replication is not taking place because this is an unsupported configuration.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6412">
				Reconfigure the replicated folder so that none of its working folders overlaps with the debug log folder.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6602" type="warning" sortkey="CONFIG_VOLUME_CONSISTENCY_CHECK_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-6602">
				Inconsistent volume configuration on <ref id="6602.4"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6602">
				The DFS Replication service detected and discarded inconsistent volume configuration on volume <ref id="6602.4"/> with error ID: <ref id="6602.2"/> (<ref id="6602.3"/>). Additional inforamtion: Inconsistent object ID <ref id="6602.5"/> and inconsistent object Type <ref id="6602.6"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6602">
				For information about troubleshooting this problem, see <str value="6602"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6702" type="warning" sortkey="customxmlmissing">
			<code _locID="code-6702">Machine configuration file for DFS Replication service has been created with default settings.</code>
			<description _locID="description-6702">The DFS Replication service did not find a valid machine configuration file at the location specified. It has created a new machine configuration file with default settings. If you made custom changes to the configuration file, such as setting a static RPC port for replication, these changes have been lost. You must recreate these changes.</description>
			<action _locID="action-6702">Use the command-line tool Dfsrdiag.exe to recreate the custom changes in the machine configuration file file.</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6802" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrnoconnections">
			<code _locID="code-6802">
				No connections are enabled for <ref id="6802.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6802">
				The DFS Replication service has detected that there are no connections enabled for replication group <ref id="6802.2"/>. No data for this replication group is replicating to or from this server.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6802">
				To resume replication, enable connections using the DFS Management snap-in or the Dfsradmin.exe command-line tool.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="6804" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrnoconnections">
			<code _locID="code-6804">
				No connections exist for <ref id="6804.2"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-6804">
				The DFS Replication service has detected that there are no connections configured for replication group <ref id="6804.2"/>. No data for this replication group is being replicated to or from this server.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6804">
				To resume replication, create connections using the DFS Management snap-in or the Dfsradmin.exe command-line tool.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9001" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_RESOURCE_CREATE_UPDATE_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-9001">
				Failed to create or update the failover cluster resource.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9001">
				The DFS Replication service failed to create / update the following failover cluster resource: <ref id="9001.4"/>. The service will retry this operation periodically. This can occur if the volume that hosts this replicated folder or its staging folder is not online. Confirm that the volumes that host the replicated folder and its staging path are online. When the required volumes are online, the service will automatically create the failover cluster resource.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9001.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9001.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9001.3"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Resource Name: <ref id="9001.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9001.5"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9001.6"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9001.7"/> ; 
				Error: <ref id="9001.8"/> (<ref id="9001.9"/>).
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-6804">
				Confirm that the volumes that host the replicated folder and its staging path are online. When the required volumes are online, the service will automatically create the failover cluster resource.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9004" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_RESOURCE_DELETE_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-9004">
				Failed to delete the failover cluster resource; no action required.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9004">
				The DFS Replication service failed to delete the following failover cluster resource: <ref id="9004.4"/>. The service will retry this operation periodically. No user action is required.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9004.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9004.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9004.3"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Resource Name: <ref id="9004.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9004.5"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9004.6"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9004.7"/> ; 
				Error: <ref id="9004.8"/> (<ref id="9004.9"/>).
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="9007" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_RESOURCE_UPDATE_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-9007">
				Failed to update failover cluster resource properties; no action required. 
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9007">
				The DFS Replication service failed to update the private properties / dependencies of the following failover cluster resource: <ref id="9007.4"/>. The service will retry this operation periodically. No user action is required.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9007.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9007.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9007.3"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Resource Name: <ref id="9007.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9007.5"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9007.6"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9007.7"/> ; 
				Error: <ref id="9007.8"/> (<ref id="9007.9"/>).
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="9009" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_RESOURCE_ONLINE_FAILED">
			<code _locID="code-9009">
				Failed to bring the failover cluster resource online; no action required.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9009">
				The DFS Replication service failed to bring the following failover cluster resource online: <ref id="9009.4"/>. The cluster service will retry the operation periodically.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9009.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9009.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9009.3"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Resource Name: <ref id="9009.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9009.5"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9009.6"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9009.7"/> ; 
				Error: <ref id="9009.8"/> (<ref id="9009.9"/>).
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="9100" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_RF_ROOT">
			<code _locID="code-9100">
				The local path of a replicated folder on a failover cluster is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9100">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the local path of a replicated folder that is hosted by a failover cluster is not valid. This can occur if the local path of the replicated folder is not on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk. 
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9100.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9100.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9100.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9100.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9100.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9100.6"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9100.7"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9100">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, delete the replicated folder <ref id="9100.2"/> from the member <ref id="9100.7"/> in the replication group <ref id="9100.4"/>. Add the replicated folder back to this replication group with a local path that is on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9101" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_NON_CLUS_RF_ROOT">
			<code _locID="code-9101">
				The local path of a replicated folder is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9101">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the local path of a replicated folder that is hosted by the local computer is not valid. This can occur if the local path of the replicated folder is on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk, but the replication group member is not a failover cluster.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9101.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9101.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9101.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9101.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9101.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9101.6"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9101">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, delete the replicated folder <ref id="9101.2"/> from the local computer in the replication group <ref id="9101.4"/>. Add the replicated folder back to the replication group with a local path that is not on a cluster shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9102" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_STAGING_PATH">
			<code _locID="code-9102">
				The local path of the staging folder on a failover cluster is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9102">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the staging folder of a replicated folder that is hosted by a failover cluster is not valid. This can occur if the path to the staging folder is not on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9102.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9102.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9102.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9102.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9102.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9102.6"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9102.7"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9102">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, change the staging folder for the replicated folder <ref id="9102.2"/> on the member <ref id="9102.7"/> in the replication group <ref id="9102.4"/>. The new staging folder must be located on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9103" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_NON_CLUS_STAGING_PATH">
			<code _locID="code-9103">
				The local path of the staging folder is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9103">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the staging folder of a replicated folder that is hosted by the local computer is not valid. This can occur if the staging folder is on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk, but the replication group member is not a failover cluster.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9103.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9103.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9103.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9103.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9103.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9103.6"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9103">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, change the staging folder for the replicated folder <ref id="9103.2"/> on this local computer in the replication group <ref id="9103.4"/>. The new staging folder must not be located on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9104" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_RF_ROOT_IN_INVALID_CLUSTER_GROUP">
			<code _locID="code-9104">
				The local path of a replicated folder is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9104">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the local path for the following replicated folder is not valid: <ref id="9104.2"/> . This can occur if the volume that hosts the replicated folder does not belong to the same cluster group as the network name resource.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9104.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9104.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9104.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9104.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9104.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9104.6"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9104.7"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9104">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, delete the replicated folder <ref id="9104.2"/> from the member <ref id="9104.7"/> in the replication group <ref id="9104.4"/>. Add the replicated folder back to this replication group so that the network name resource for the member and the volume that hosts the replicated folder are in the same cluster group.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9105" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_STAGING_PATH_IN_INVALID_CLUSTER_GROUP">
			<code _locID="code-9105">
				The local path of the staging folder is not valid.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9105">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the staging path for the following replicated folder is not valid: <ref id="9105.2"/>. This can occur if the volume that hosts the staging folder does not belong to the same cluster group as the network name resource.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9105.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9105.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9105.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9105.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9105.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9105.6"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9105.7"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9105">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, change the path of the staging folder for the replicated folder <ref id="9105.2"/> on the member <ref id="9105.7"/> in the replication group <ref id="9105.4"/>. The volume that hosts the new staging folder and the network name resource must belong to the same cluster group.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9106" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_VCO_TO_NODE_REPLICATION">
			<code _locID="code-9106">
				A failover cluster and a node in the cluster cannot belong to the same replication group.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9106">
				The DFS Replication service detected that a virtual computer object and a node in the same failover cluster are members of the same replication group. This is not a supported configuration and will cause replication to fail.
				Additional information:
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9106.1"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9106.2"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9106.3"/> ; 
				Node Name: <ref id="9106.4"/>.
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="9107" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_INVALID_INTER_VCO_REPLICATION">
			<code _locID="code-9107">
				Two clustered file server instances on the same failover cluster cannot belong to the same replication group.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9107">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the replication group <ref id="9107.1"/> has members (<ref id="9107.3"/> and <ref id="9107.4"/>) which are network names that belong to the same failover cluster. This is an unsupported configuration and will cause replication to fail.
				Additional information:
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9107.1"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9107.2"/> ; 
				Network Name 1: <ref id="9107.3"/> ; 
				Network Name 2: <ref id="9107.4"/>.
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="9108" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_SYSVOL_ON_SHARED_DISK">
			<code _locID="code-9108">
				The local path for the SYSVOL replicated folder cannot be on a shared disk.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9108">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the local path for the SYSVOL replicated folder is not valid. This can occur if the SYSVOL local path is on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk. This is an unsupported configuration.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9108.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9108.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9108.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9108.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9108.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9108.6"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9108">
				Demote and re-promote this domain controller using a SYSVOL local path on a volume that belongs to a non-shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9109" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_SYSVOL_STAGING_ON_SHARED_DISK">
			<code _locID="code-9109">
				The staging folder for the SYSVOL replicated folder cannot be on a shared disk.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9109">
				The DFS Replication service detected that the staging path for the SYSVOL replicated folder is not valid. This can occur if the volume that is hosting the staging folder is on a volume that belongs to a cluster shared disk. This is an unsupported configuration.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9109.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9109.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9109.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9109.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9109.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9109.6"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9109">
				Using the DFS Management MMC snap-in, change the path of the staging folder for the SYSVOL folder <ref id="9109.2"/> on this domain controller. The new staging folder must be located on a volume that belongs to a non-shared disk.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="9110" type="error" sortkey="DFSR_CLUSTER_CONFIG_DISK_NOT_ONLINE">
			<code _locID="code-9110">
				The staging folder or local path of a replicated folder cannot be verified.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-9110">
				The DFS Replication service cannot verify the root or staging path of a replicated folder that is hosted by a failover cluster. This can occur if the shared disk hosting the root or staging path of the replicated folder is not online.
				Additional information:
				Replicated Folder Name: <ref id="9110.1"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder Path: <ref id="9110.2"/> ; 
				Replicated Folder ID: <ref id="9110.3"/> ; 
				Replication Group Name: <ref id="9110.4"/> ; 
				Replication Group ID: <ref id="9110.5"/> ; 
				Staging Folder Path: <ref id="9110.6"/> ; 
				Network Name: <ref id="9110.7"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-9110">
				Using the Failover cluster Management UI, online the disk hosting the replicated folder <ref id="9110.7"/> from the member <ref id="9110.7"/> in the replication group <ref id="9110.4"/>. Once the disk is online and available then DFSR will be able to verify the paths and start replicating.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10001" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrrepwmiaccessdenied" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10001">Cannot access the local WMI repository. </code>
			<description _locID="description-10001">Due to an Access Denied error, the DFS Replication reporting mechanism cannot access the WMI (Windows Management Instrumentation) namespace to retrieve certain reporting information.</description>
			<action _locID="action-10001">Verify that you are a member of the local Administrators group on this server. </action>
		</error>
		<error id="10002" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrrepwmierror" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10002">Cannot access the local WMI repository. </code>
			<description _locID="description-10002">
				Due to the following error, the DFS Replication reporting mechanism cannot access the WMI (Windows Management Instrumentation) namespace to retrieve certain reporting information. Error ID: <ref id="10002.1"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10002">
				For information about troubleshooting WMI errors, see <str value="wmi"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10003" type="error" sortkey="dfsrsvcnotinstalled" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10003">
				The DFS Replication service is not installed on <str value="servername"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-10003">The DFS Replication service is not installed on this server. No replicated folders are replicating to or from this server. </description>
			<action _locID="action-10003">
				Ensure that Windows Server 2003 R2 is installed on this server and that the DFS Replication service was installed using Add or Remove Programs.
				If Windows Server 2003 R2 is installed, you can use the following procedure to install the DFS Replication service: <ol>
					<li>
						In <b>Add or Remove Programs</b>, click <b>Add/Remove Windows Components</b>.
					</li>
					<li>
						In the Windows Components Wizard, click <b>Distributed File System</b>, and then click <b>Details</b>.
					</li>
					<li>
						Click <b>DFS Replication service</b>, click OK, and then complete the wizard.
					</li>
				</ol>
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10004" type="error" sortkey="dfsrsvcstopped" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10004">The DFS Replication service is stopped. </code>
			<description _locID="description-10004">The DFS Replication service is stopped. No replicated folders are replicating to or from this server. </description>
			<action _locID="action-10004">
				Restart the DFS Replication service either by using the Services snap-in or by typing <b>net start dfsr</b> at the command prompt.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10005" type="error" sortkey="dfsrsvcdisabled" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10005">The DFS Replication service is disabled. </code>
			<description _locID="description-10005">The DFS Replication service is disabled. No replicated folders are replicating to or from this server. </description>
			<action _locID="action-10005">
				In the Services snap-in, do the following: <ol>
					<li>
						Double-click <b>DFS Replication service</b>.
					</li>
					<li>
						On the <b>General</b> tab, in <b>Startup type</b>, click <b>Automatic</b>.
					</li>
					<li>
						To start the DFS Replication service, click <b>Start</b>.
					</li>
				</ol>
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10007" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrrepwmicannotaccess" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10007">Cannot access the local WMI repository.</code>
			<description _locID="description-10007">
				The DFS Replication reporting mechanism cannot find the WMI (Windows Management Instrumentation) namespace to retrieve certain reporting information. Error ID: <ref id="10007.1"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10007">
				For information about troubleshooting WMI errors, see <str value="wmi"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10008" type="warning" sortkey="dfsrrepwmicannotaccess" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10008">Cannot access the local WMI repository.</code>
			<description _locID="description-10008">
				DFS Replication reporting mechanism cannot access the WMI (Windows Management Instrumentation) namespace to retrieve certain reporting information because of timeout. Error ID: <ref id="10008.1"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10008">
				For information about troubleshooting WMI errors, see <str value="wmi"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10016" type="warning" sortkey="ErrorReadingData" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10016">Unable to access required data source.</code>
			<description _locID="description-10016">
				The DFS Replication reporting mechanism cannot access a required data source. Error ID: <ref id="10016.1"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10016">
				Please verify proper access permissions. For information about troubleshooting backlog errors, see <str value="10016"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10017" type="error" sortkey="cannotaccessperfcounters" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10017">Cannot access DFS Replication performance counters. </code>
			<description _locID="description-10017">
				The DFS Replication service is unable to access the performance counter <ref id="10017.2"/> on <str value="servername"/>. Performance data is unavailable. Error ID: <ref id="10017.1"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10017">
				Please verify that the DFSR service is started, that the DFSR WMI provider is registered and the performance counters are available locally by loading them into PerfMon. If you suspect that the performance counters are corrupt, please refer to KB article 300956 <str value="10017"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10020" type="warning" sortkey="backlogcalerror" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10020">
				Backlog counts are unavailable due to failure. <ref id="message"/>
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-10020">
				A failure occurred while the reporting mechanism processed version vectors on the reference member. Version vectors are used to compare how up-to-date this server is compared to the reference server. If version vectors cannot be processed, then the backlog, if any, cannot be determined <ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-10020">
				For information about troubleshooting backlog errors, see <str value="10020"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="10021" type="warning" sortkey="memberininitsyncstate" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-10021">
				This member is waiting for initial replication for replicated folder <ref id="10021.1"/>.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-10021">
				This member is waiting for initial replication for replicated folder <ref id="10021.1"/> and is not currently participating in replication. This delay can occur because the member is waiting for the DFS Replication service to retrieve replication settings from Active Directory Domain Services. After the member detects that it is part of replication group, the member will begin initial replication.
            </description>
			<action _locID="action-10021">
				Replication will begin after initial replication is complete. If this state does not change, see <str value="10021"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="11001" type="warning" sortkey="lowdiskspace" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-11001">
				Volume <ref id="11001.2"/> is low on disk space.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-11001">
				Volume <ref id="11001.2"/> is low on disk space. If this volume becomes full, the DFS Replication service will stop replication on the volume. <ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-11001">
				Increase available disk space on the specified volume or move the replicated folder to a different volume. See additional information about disk space under the informational section in the table titled "Current used and free disk space on volumes where replicated folders are stored. 
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="11002" type="warning" sortkey="missing_rpc_fix" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-11002">
			The RPC hotfix is not installed on this server.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-11002">
			This hotfix addresses RPC issues that can cause the DFS Replication service to fail, possibly without corresponding failure events in the DFS Replication event log. If the DFS Replication service does not restart automatically, replication backlogs can occur that are not easily attributed to RPC issues. Therefore, we highly recommend that you install this hotfix on all servers participating in DFS Replication.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-11002">
				To learn more about this fix and how to obtain it, see <str value="11002"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="11003" type="warning" sortkey="pre-exisitng" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-11003">
        		Pre-existing content is not replicated and is consuming disk space.
			</code>
			<description _locID="description-11003">
				During the initial replication process for replicated folder <ref id="11003.2"/>, the DFS Replication service identified pre-existing local content that was not present on the primary member and moved the content to <ref id="11003.1"/>. The DfsrPrivate\Preexisting folder is a hidden system folder that is located under the local path of the replicated folder. Content in the DfsrPrivate\PreExisting folder will not be replicated to other members of the replication group, nor will the content be deleted by the DFS Replication service during any automatic clean-up.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-11003">
				If you want this content to be replicated to other members, move the content into the replicated folder outside of the DfsrPrivate folder. If you want to reclaim this disk space, delete the pre-existing content in the PreExisting folder.
			</action>
		</error>
    <error id="11004" type="error" refers2="filtered" reports="none" sortkey="sharingviolations">
      <code _locID="code-11004">One or more replicated folders have content skipped by DFS Replication. </code>
      <description _locID="description-11004">
        DFS Replication does not replicate certain files in the replicated folders listed above because they have temporary attribute set, or they are symbolic links . This problem is affecting at least <str value="filecount"/> files in <str value="setcount"/> replicated folders (up to 100 occurences per replicated folder are reported).
      </description>
      <action _locID="action-11004">
        Verify that the files you want to replicate are not temporary and not symbolic links. 
      </action>
    </error>
    <!-- WMI Server Errors -->
		<error id="cannotGetVVs" type="error" sortkey="cannotgetversionvec" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotGetVVs">Cannot retrieve version vectors from this member.</code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotGetVVs">
				Backlog calculations cannot be performed because an error occurred while the reporting mechanism attempted to retrieve version vectors from this member: <ref id="message"/>. Version vectors are used to compare how up-to-date this server is compared to the reference server. If version vectors cannot be processed, then the backlog, if any, cannot be determined.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-cannotGetVVs">
				For information about troubleshooting backlog problems, see <str value="getvv"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="cannotGetBacklogs" type="error" sortkey="cannotgetbacklogcal" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotGetBacklogs">Cannot retrieve inbound version vectors from this member.</code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotGetBacklogs">
				Inbound backlog calculations cannot be performed because the following error occurred while the reporting mechanism attempted to retrieve version vectors from this member: <ref id="message"/> Version vectors are used to compare how up-to-date this server is compared to the reference server. If version vectors cannot be processed, then the backlog, if any, cannot be determined.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-cannotGetBacklogs">
				For information about troubleshooting backlog problems, see <str value="getbacklog"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="zeroReferenceContentSet" type="warning" sortkey="zerocontentseterror" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-zeroReferenceContentSet">Reference member returned no replicated folders. </code>
			<description _locID="description-zeroReferenceContentSet">Backlog calculations cannot be performed because the reference member returned zero replicated folders. </description>
			<action _locID="action-zeroReferenceContentSet">
				For information about troubleshooting backlog problems, see <str value="0cs"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="cannotGetVVsWmiError" type="error" sortkey="cannotgetversionvecwmierror" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotGetVVsWmiError">Cannot retrieve version vectors from this member due to a Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) error. </code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotGetVVsWmiError">
				Backlog calculations cannot be performed because DFS Replication encountered the following error while accessing the Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) repository to retrieve version vectors from this member: <ref id="message"/>, see <str value="wmi"/> to resolve the error string.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-cannotGetVVsWmiError">
				For information about troubleshooting WMI access issues, <str value="wmi"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="cannotGetBacklogsWmiError" type="error" sortkey="cannotgetbacklogcalwmierror" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotGetBacklogsWmiError">Cannot get inbound backlogs from this member due to a Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) error.</code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotGetBacklogsWmiError">
				Inbound backlog counts cannot be determined because DFS Replication encountered the following error while accessing the Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) to retrieve backlog counts from this member: <ref id="message"/>.
			</description>
			<action _locID="action-cannotGetBacklogsWmiError">
				For information about troubleshooting WMI access issues, see <str value="wmi"/> to resolve the error string.
			</action>
		</error>
		<!-- Unavailable Server Errors -->
		<error id="cannotConnect" type="unvailableServerError" sortkey="cannotconn" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotConnect">Cannot connect to reporting DCOM server. </code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotConnect">
				<ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action _locID="description-cannotConnect"> 
			Verify that the DFS Replication Service is installed on the server and that RPC traffic is not blocked by firewalls or port filtering. For information about troubleshooting RPC issues see <str value="rpckb"/>.
			</action>
		</error>
		<error id="cannotGetReport" type="unvailableServerError" sortkey="cannotgetr" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotGetReport">Cannot retrieve report.</code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotGetReport">
				<ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="cannotUncompressReport" type="unvailableServerError" sortkey="cannotunco" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-cannotUncompressReport">Cannot uncompress report.</code>
			<description _locID="description-cannotUncompressReport">
				<ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
		<error id="notLocalAdmin" type="unvailableServerError" sortkey="notlocalad" hideeventid="true">
			<code _locID="code-notLocalAdmin">Not a local administrator.</code>
			<description _locID="description-notLocalAdmin">
				<ref id="message"/>
			</description>
			<action/>
		</error>
	</ecset>
</staticData>
